# KENDALL CLARK

Kendallclarkdev@gmail.com | 213-399-3200 | Sherman Oaks, CA 91403

https://kendallclarkdev.github.io/Kendall-Clark-portfolio/

# Summary

Hello!! I'm a Ux/UI Designer with a talent for Making User-centered Designs from Phone Apps to web pages. With a strong knowledge of User Research and Prototyping as well As Building/Coding . I am very communicative and team-oriented with proficiency in HTML/CSS/JS with a Proven history of fostering Planning and design to meet team, individual and management objectives.

## **Skills**

Time management
Project planning
Web Development(HTML5/CSS/Javascript)
User-centered Design
User Experience (UX)
User Research

Front-end Development Adobe XD, Figma, Sketch Teamwork Communication Usability testing Critical thinking

# **Experience**

UX Lead | Genius Diagnostics (AI) | 10/2021 - 11/2021

- Consulting with clients to understand their goals and explaining research results
- · Conducting usability testing
- Creating wireframes, storyboards, sitemaps and screen flows
- Creating product prototypes
- Developing personas and usage scenarios
- Analyzing user feedback and activity, and iterating to enhance the user experience
- Assisting with content development
- Conducting competitor and customer analysis

#### UI Lead Designer | Career Carrot Remote | 08/2021 - 09/2021

- plan and implement new designs
- Optimize existing user interface designs
- Test for intuitivity and experience
- Communicate with clients to understand their business goals and objectives
- Develop technical and business requirements and always strive to deliver intuitive and user-centered solutions
- Combine creativity with an awareness of the design elements
- Create prototypes for new product ideas

### Front-End Web Developer | Domecity tv (Podcast) - Remote | 07/2021 - 08/2021

- Created successful websites that met requirements for objectives such as load speed and design.
- Collaborated with customers to determine needs and work through design options.
- Gathered, defined and translated client requirements into product stories and actionable tasks.
- Monitored website performance to quickly rectify front-end-related issues.
- Brought mock-ups to life with HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

## Social Media Manager | Dental For You - Dallas, TX | 10/2018 - 08/2019

- Develop, implement and manage our social media strategy
- Define most important social media KPIs
- Manage and oversee social media content
- Measure the success of every social media campaign
- Stay up to date with latest social media best practices and technologies
- Use social media marketing tools such as Buffer.

# **Education and Training**

Northside High School | Warner Robins, GA | 05/2014

High School Diploma

<u>Northwest University</u> | Kirkland, WA **Some College (No Degree)**: Social Psychology

General Assembly | Los Angeles, CA | 11/2021

User Experience Design : Ux/UI Design